topic = "Prepositions with verbs (p3).";
grammar = "Dream ABOUT (while sleeping), OF (while imaginating)<br>";
grammar+= "Hear ABOUT (be told about smth)<br>";
grammar+= "Hear OF (know thath smd/smth exists<br>";
grammar+= "Hear FROM (receive letter/call from smb)<br>";
grammar+= "Think ABOUT smth (consider/concentrate)<br>";
grammar+= "Think OF smth (idea popping)<br>";
grammar+= "Sometimes you could use both<br>";
grammar+= "Remind ABOUT (not to forget)<br>";
grammar+= "Remind OF (cause smbd to remember)<br>";
grammar+= "Complain TO smbd ABOUT smth (being not satisfied)<br>";
grammar+= "Complain TO smdd OF pain/illness<br>";
grammar+= "Warn smb OF/ABOUT danger/bad to happen<br>";
lol="I need to check it, page 277. Looks like the same";
lol+=" with a teacher";
grammar+= "Warn smb about dangerous/unusual<br>"; 

cards = [
 {"question":"Last night I was dreaming ... taking an exam. Terrific experience!",
  "answer": "about",
  "radios": ["about", "of", "on", "no preposition"],
 },
 {"question":"Sometimes I'm daydreaming ... moving to Mexico",
  "answer": "of",
  "radios": ["about", "of", "on", "no preposition"],
 },
 {"question":"I heard ... the last news",
  "answer": "about",
  "radios": ["about", "of", "on", "no preposition"],
 },
 {"question":"I heard ... those spiders. Their venom is the best!",
  "answer": "of",
  "radios": ["about", "of", "on", "no preposition"],
 },
 {"question":"I never heard ... of here. Who is she?",
  "answer": "of",
  "radios": ["about", "of", "on", "no preposition"],
 },
 {"question":"I thought ... writing a book for 2 weeks",
  "answer": "about",
  "radios": ["about", "of", "for", "no preposition"],
 },
 {"question":"I thought ... going there for a moment",
  "answer": "of",
  "radios": ["about", "of", "for", "no preposition"],
 },
 {"question":"I am thinking ... moving to Mexico",
  "answer": ["about", "of"],
  "radios": ["about", "of", "for", "no preposition"],
  "comment": "the prep depends on<br>how seriousthe one think about that",
  "showcomment": "yes",
 },
 {"question":"Could you remind me ... our agreement in 2 days before?",
  "answer": "about",
  "radios": ["about", "of", "for", "no preposition"],
 },
 {"question":"This photo reminded me ... my hometown",
  "answer": "of",
  "radios": ["about", "of", "for", "no preposition"],
 },
 {"question":"This photo reminded me ... my hometown",
  "answer": "of",
  "radios": ["about", "of", "for", "no preposition"],
 },
 {"question":"I'm always complaining to Sonya ... girls freezing out",
  "answer": "about",
  "radios": ["about", "of", "for", "no preposition"],
 },
 {"question":"I'm always complaining to Sonya ... my spine aching",
  "answer": "of",
  "radios": ["about", "of", "for", "no preposition"],
 },
 {"question":"Everybody has been warned ... the dangers of smoking",
  "answer": ["of", "about"],
  "radios": ["about", "of", "for", "no preposition"],
 },
 {"question":"I was warned ... her. She is an ex-sniper",
  "answer": "about",
  "radios": ["about", "of", "for", "no preposition"],
 },
 {"question":"Google Maps warned me ... a traffic jam",
  "answer": "about",
  "radios": ["about", "of", "for", "no preposition"],
 },
]

include("js/engine.js",function(){
  //
});

